Lord Yevgraf.
Oh?
It seems the one who was with you got away.
No matter.
I only need one.
Are you finally awake, Mikhail?
I don't know how you can sleep when we're finally headed to see our master!
I'm so excited that I couldn't possible get a wink!
I can't stop thinking back to that scene.
We're here!
However...
That ends today.
Lord Yevgraf!
To think that you would come to greet us yourself!
I am so very honored!
I've been waiting for you, Mikhail.
Were you lonely without me?
Wh-Wha—
How dare you speak to him like that!
I see you haven't changed.
Ah, yes, yes! Let's go!
W-Wait—
Let us proceed, Mikhail.
To the final hope of our race.
To the Ark of Sirius!
If I'm to live
by inertia
There's probably nothing
wrong with giving up
But I don't want the night stolen from me
The moon shines down on me as if to comfort my shuttered heart
I'm left with only a cold blade
I'm just losing myself
I'm searching
Just like this planet that's lost everything
I don't think that I'm always right
But I'm not going to regret what I do now
Making just one wish, I fade into the night
It sure is cold.
Moving to Karafuto at this time of year?
We must both not be right in the head.
I'm not sure I could handle it if my family weren't with me.
Same here.
It's likely that Yevgraf is close to finding the Ark.
Or perhaps he already has.
What? But how?
The ancient text?
Yes.
The original was recovered several centuries ago from what are believed to be ruins of Sirius civilization.
I wasn't able to decipher all of it,
but I did find information on the Ark of Sirius.
Things like what the Ark was and how it was passed down.
But by the time Yevgraf attacked Dogville,
someone had already taken it elsewhere.
My dad, right?
Yes.
I thought that with no lead as to where he went, they'd be stuck.
But it seems that they never gave up.
So you think they finished deciphering the text?
And there was something in there that indicated where he took it?
That seems most likely.
I assume they replicated my methods.
Yuliy.
Until now, I've thought of nothing but driving the vampires to extinction.
I thought I could atone for what I did to you and Dogville that way.
Professor...
South Karafuto.
Yevgraf is waiting there.
As well as the Ark of Sirius.
Your little brother and that professor have been working as Jaegers. Quite a turn of events.
How was he? He must be about as tall as you now, yes?
Why are you asking me about that?
I ordered that all Jaegers be killed on sight.
You had plenty of chances,
but you never pulled the trigger, so to speak.
Your little brother must be very precious to you.
What's this?
An ancient syllabary that the Sirius once used.
The Sirius?
In the distant past, this land was home to a flourishing Sirius civilization.
Naturally, then, this is hallowed ground to the Sirius.
And so, when your father spirited the Ark away, he took it here.
What?
The writing on the walls says that this land is where the Ark of Sirius was born
and the only place where it can be sealed away.
Sealed?
My father never said a word about that.
What, did he tell you that he'd come right back after he tucked the Ark away somewhere?
But your father never returned to Dogville.
And you are about to find out why, Mikhail.
What is this?
It would be no exaggeration to say that the choice your father made as the bearer of the Ark
was an act that the Sirius would consider most heroic.
If a human or any of our kind were to get any closer to it,
I frankly don't know what would happen to them.
There is some kind of barrier here, powered by the Ark itself.
Your father created it in exchange for his own life.
Dad did?
An eternal seal, unbreakable to all the world.
But as both a Sirius and his beloved son,
I believe you may be the exception.
Now, it's time for you to reunite with your father!
Somewhere in this land...
So you're telling us that Yuliy just left us to look for this
"Ark of Sirius"? To southern Karafuto of all places?
Most likely.
Well, he's never lacked for spunk.
He didn't need to just run off without telling us!
Down, boy.
I keep telling you not to mess with my hair!
I gotta say, I never took him for a treasure hunter.
We don't even know what's in the thing.
It doesn't matter what's inside it.
It's probably just that discovering it has become his reason to live now.
And he doesn't want us to have any part of it, huh?
Professor, should we really just leave Yuliy alone on this?
I mean he's strong, but I think this is too much for him to handle by himself.
"We have our orders," huh?
Philip!
Going back to Headquarters is more important than Yuliy, right?
Right.
Why—
However...
We have someplace to go first.
We're going to do what only we can.
Let me know once you've decided on your order.
'Scuse me, miss. Mind bringing me some sake?
Yes, coming right up.
You really shouldn't drink this much during the day.
I don't wanna hear it. I can't deal with this sober.
Welcome!
Stop right there.
No reason to start flashing that around in a place like this.
I've gotta say, you have some sharp eyes.
This place has the tastiest food in south Karafuto.
Come on. I'll treat you, so just don't start barking my head off,
Yuliy Jirov.
You're...
Bishop.
We're in the same trade.
You're a Jaeger.
Both the Ark and Dad are resting here.
He gave his life in order to seal the Ark.
And now I'm going to break that seal?
What's wrong? Hurry up and pull your beloved father out of there.
I'm sorry, Dad.
With the Ark...
If I get the Ark, then I can kill him!
Why, Dad?
Dad...
Please!
Let me...
Let me use... The Ark...
Enough.
Come back, Mikhail.
I refuse!
Stop—
It would be boring for you to die here.
Don't...
interfere!
You're as obstinate a servant as ever.
I've never once considered myself your servant!
The effect of the blood of the noble Sirius still running through your veins, perhaps?
However...
Even that nobility cannot stand in the face of our blood pact!
Unfortunately, it seems that pact has bought you the hatred of your father.
But how will your precious little brother fare, I wonder?
Wiped out?
No need to shout.
All the other Jaegers were killed?
Come on, don't look like that. I'm still alive, at least.
But man, I can't believe I made a request for reinforcements and got just you.
You're mistaken.
I didn't come here as a Jaeger.
So you're after the Ark of Sirius, I guess?
How do you...
Come on, we're coworkers.
I usually end up hearing about everyone's history one way or another.
Including the fact that you're a remnant of the Sirius.
How much do you know?
Just that the Ark exists at all.
I found out when I was chasing Yevgraf.
Disappointed?
No.
Well, how about this.
This very evening, I'm planning on contacting someone who knows what happened to the Ark.
You want information on the Ark.
I want to find the Ark before Yevgraf does,
break it before his very eyes, and then break him.
For the most part, our interests are aligned.
You're suggesting we team up?
It never hurts to have someone to trust your back to.
All right.
But the Ark is something precious to my race.
I don't want it broken.
Lord Yevgraf, you've returned!
How did it go?
So it didn't work after all.
Lord Yevgraf, a moment please!
We have no time to lose!
If recovering the Ark is proving troublesome even with a Sirius,
we have but one path left before us!
A moment!
Now is the time for the results of my grand research to prove...
To prove...
The destruction of the prototype was unfortunate,
but with your permission, I can start mass-production at any time!
Lord Yevgraf, your orders!
Lord Yevgraf...
I swear...
I swear that I'll prove my research was worthwhile to you.
It's my research that will give vampires a future!
On fall evening winds.
Flying from the capital.
Strangers to this land.
Those people were like a typhoon.
Hopefully Ryouko will calm down a bit now that—
Baron!
What is it? You're too loud.
I-I found this!
To Father
Dearest Father, I hope this finds you well.
My preparations being complete, I will now set out for London.
Father, your Ryouko must go on a trip.
Please forgive me for leaving without telling you.
Discovering the true nature of the disaster that befell our house is, I believe,
my responsibility as the next head of the family.
By unrelenting effort and spirit,
I swear to you I will finish this task and return to you.
Until that time comes, please stay well.
With love, Ryouko.
Wh-What are we going to do?
"If you love your child, allow them their journeys," as they say.
Right, let's go!
Where?
Need it be said?
To London!
What was all that about allowing them their journeys?
Nobody's ever said that you can't go with them!
Oh, of course!
Being sent to Karafuto this time of year smells like a demotion.
It feels like I'm between a rock and a hard place.
How things turn from here depends entirely on the Ark.
I need to keep myself fed to stay well-fueled for this trip!
It's too cold for these old bones.
Winter's come early this year.
There's really someone who knows about the Ark this deep in the mountains?
He's apparently an eccentric old recluse.
He might not be willing to talk to us.
By the way, what's your weapon?
You fight with those sticks?
Who taught you?
Your group's leader?
I'm self-taught.
That's not what I want to hear.
But the Professor taught me most everything else.
How to read and write, all kinds of words, and...
How to kill vampires?
Not sure about a professor who'd teach crap like that to a kid.
I'm sure that we're going to end up fighting together at some point.
Can I ask you something before that happens?
What's that?
If you ask me a stupid question like "can you shoot," I'll whack you.
I smell the scent of blood on you.
The same smell that they have.
Are you really a Jaeger?
When you do this job for a long time,
their smell starts sticking to you permanently.
Some use cologne to hide it. I use my cigar.
I always knew that I'd have to pay one day for killing so many.
But I didn't expect to have to pay the whole bill at once.
Are you talking about how your team died?
Yeah.
I spent more time with them than my actual family.
Same's true for you, yeah?
Yes.
That's why...
I came alone.
Hey.
We're here.
Crap!
Shit!
Damned monsters!
Don't worry about me, Yuliy!
Are you all right?
I'm Larissa.
I'm Tamara.
You're Misha's little brother, right?
You don't look the same at all!
Why don't you become a vampire, too?
You'll be able to play with Misha again!
Shut the hell up!
Why not?
Why're you angry?
Do you hate us?
Because we killed all those villagers?
Because you're the only Sirius left?
Shut up!
A Sirius?
Because your mom got killed?
But Misha got to be a vampire!
If Lord Yevgraf hadn't bitten him, he woulda died!
Yevgraf did it?
He turned my brother into...
Aren't you lonely, Yuliy?
It'll be all right, Yuliy!
Just form a blood pact with us!
What an unbearable end
I breath out, breath out, breath out, and stop
As I'm fleeing from this cruel world, I fall into a deep sleep
I hide behind the words "I'm doing my best"
But in the end I do nothing but look back
Even when I feel like I've been able to change,
Eventually I realize that the only thing that's changed is the position of the stars
I find myself wondering if everything would feel better if I just broke
Before I fade away while thinking of you,
If I dig out all of my pain then I'll be able to shine like a real star
Will I find a beautiful dream?
This is how we embrace hope
There may be more infected.
Why did you hesitate?
You won't be able to get your hands on the Ark.
Hurry up and die!
Thanks to what Alexei did, nobody will.
What are dads like?